gowildcasino.com 2016-10-26

# GoWild Casino Privacy Policy

This website (the "Site") is operated by and information gathered from this Site is collected by GoWild Casino Malta Ltd, a company incorporated and based in Malta (company registration no. C43606) ("GoWild Casino", "us" or "we"). GoWild Casino respects the privacy of its online visitors and users of the Site. GoWild Casino recognizes the importance of protecting certain information collected from users and has adopted this Privacy Policy to explain how GoWild Casino gathers, stores, and uses information provided by users through the Sites as described below. 

## ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY POLICY

If you use the Site, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and GoWild Casino will have the right to use your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to have your information used in any of the ways described in this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use of the Site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Site, after we either personally notify you or generally post changes on the Site, will constitute your acceptance of those changes.

## Cookie Policy

**What Are Cookies**   
Like the majority of websites, we use cookies to a limited extent to enhance the user experience, provide customization and useful features to our site and products. We also use standard analytics software to help us learn how our users are interacting with the website.   
This page describes how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies.   
We will also share how you can prevent these cookies from being stored however, this may block certain elements of the sites functionality. 

**How We Use Cookies**   
Knowing more about you, helps us give you more of what you want. More exclusive offers, more information, and more control.   
There are no industry standard options for disabling cookies without completely disabling the functionality and features they add to the site. It is recommended that you leave on all cookies if you are unsure of whether you need them or not. We know that personal information is valuable and needs to be treated with care. Be assured that your personal data will not be disclosed, to any third party. 

**Disabling Cookies**   
You can prevent cookies by adjusting your browser settings but keep in mind that disabling cookies will usually result in also disabling certain functionality and features of this site and many other websites that you visit, such as the ability to log in or play games. Therefore, it is recommended that you do not disable cookies. 

**The Cookies We Set**   
When creating an account with us, we will use cookies for the management of the sign-up process and general account administration. The cookies are usually deleted when you log out, however, in some cases they may remain to help remember your site preferences when logged out. This prevents you from having to log in every single time you visit a new page.   
When you submit data through a form such as those found on the contact pages, cookies may be set to remember your user details for future correspondence. 

**Third Party Cookies**   
We use Google as our trusted analytics solution to help us understand how you use the site and the ways in which we can improve your experience. These cookies may track aspects such as how long you spend on our site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce the most enticing and engaging content.   
We do have partners who advertise on our behalf and affiliate tracking cookies help us track if our customers have come to our site through one of our partners and this way, we can credit them appropriately. Sometimes, the cookies allow our affiliate partners to provide bonuses that they may offer to customers for their interaction. 

**More Info**   
We hope that has clarified the cookies usage for you and as we mentioned before, if there is something that you are not completely sure of, it is safer to leave cookies enabled. If you are still looking for more information, please contact us.

## PUBLIC MESSAGES

Any information that is disclosed in a public area of the Site by users is public information and users should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information on the Site. If you voluntarily disclose information in a public area of the Site, such as a message board, that information may be collected and used by a third-party to send you unsolicited messages, advertisements or for other purposes. We do not control the actions of these third parties in public areas of the Site, so if you disclose information in a public area, you do so at your own risk.

## CHOICE/OPT-OUT

GoWild Casino may use customer contact information provided by you to send information about GoWild Casino and the products, Services and/or Sites for which you subscribed or otherwise used or accessed, including news about product updates, contests, events, and other promotional materials. If you have given us your consent, we will also send communications for unrelated products or Services. 

GoWild Casino provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from GoWild Casino, when you are asked to provide information to us. In addition, GoWild Casino gives users the option of discontinuing receipt of communications from GoWild Casino. Instructions for discontinuing receipt of communications from GoWild Casino will be made available with each communication from GoWild Casino or on the related Site.

## INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER, STORAGE AND SECURITY OF INFORMATION

GoWild Casino will take reasonable steps to protect the information users share with us. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure.

## COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION

We may require your personal information for access to certain parts of the Site and related products or Services. We may collect your personal information when you: (a) register to become a member or user of our Services; (b) voluntarily provide it when you use the Site; (c) disclose it in a public area of the Site; or (d) provide it when you communicate with us. 

If you register to become a member or user of our Services through the Site, we may use the personal information that you provide for billing purposes, and to administer and manage your account and provide promotional updates regarding such products or Services as contemplated above. 

GoWild Casino may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical, Service or security issues related to a product or Service you requested, confirming you requested a product or Service, or providing periodic updates or information relating to the product or Service you requested. For so long as you are subscribed to a Service, you will not be able to choose to unsubscribe from these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the Service you have chosen. 

GoWild Casino may occasionally hire other companies to provide limited Services on our behalf, including without limitation, identity verification, payment processing and the provision of software. GoWild Casino will only provide these companies that information which is reasonably required to perform the Service, and they will be prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. 

Generally, when our third-party contractors or partners collect and/or have access to your personal information we require that they adhere to our stated privacy policies and protect the confidentiality of your personal information. 

GoWild Casino may elect to share your personal information with qualified third-party partners for marketing or other similar purposes but only where you agree to share such information. Such partners will be prohibited from disclosing or using such information except for the limited purposes which the users have consented to. 

The Site contains links to third-party websites. When you follow these links you leave the Site and are transferred to a third party website. You should be aware that these third-party websites may have their own information collection practices and privacy policies. We do not control the privacy policies of third parties that have websites linked to the Site. 

If you follow a third-party advertisement or link, the privacy policies of the third-party website that you are linked to will prevail. The Privacy Policy does not extend to these external websites and companies. Please refer directly to the privacy policies on such third party websites. 

We assume no responsibility or liability for the actions of such third parties with respect to their use of your information or otherwise. Accordingly, please make sure you are aware of and comfortable with the privacy policies of any third-party websites to which you are transferred by following a link. 

GoWild Casino may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process or any governmental request; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of GoWild Casino or its affiliated companies; (c) enforce the Terms and Conditions; or (d) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of GoWild Casino' employees, users of the Site, or members of the public. 

By using the Site, users agree that GoWild Casino may share with other parties aggregate information and non-identifiable information gathered by GoWild Casino in the course of the continuing use of the Site. Aggregate information or non-identifiable information may be used to improve the Site, for internal marketing studies, or simply to collect demographic information about users.

## NO ABSOLUTE SAFEGUARDS

Although we will use reasonable efforts to safeguard the privacy of your information, transmissions on the internet cannot be made absolutely secure. Accordingly, we assume no responsibility or liability for disclosure of any of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access or other causes beyond our reasonable control.

## YOUR ROLE IN PROTECTING YOUR PRIVACY

Please remember that protection of your privacy begins with you. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any account ID or password you use to register, and you should always be careful and responsible whenever disclosing information online. 

Corrections, Updates and Removal of Information If you are concerned with the accuracy of the personal information provided by you and maintained by GoWild Casino or would like your personal information removed from GoWild Casino records, you may use the tools made available on the Site to update or remove such information. 

GoWild Casino reserves the right to charge a reasonable fee for supplying copies of such information. If you choose to delete your personal information, you may not be able to access some areas of the Site and/or Services to which you have subscribed. We will not provide a refund for any prepaid Service which is inaccessible to you because of the deletion of your personal information. We may, however, still retain your personal information in our files to resolve disputes, to enforce our user agreement, and to comply with any and all technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of the Site.
